dacast.com 2019-12-19

# Privacy Policy - DaCast Video Hosting & Live Streaming Solutions

Last updated: June 10, 2010

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand how DACAST, its subsidiary and affiliate corporations, successors, and assigns (collectively referred to as “DACAST”) use and protect the information you provide. This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) applies to this World Wide Web site and any variations or successors to this website (www.DACAST.com, the “DACAST Site”), any DACAST computer software downloadable or otherwise available from the DACAST Site (“DACAST Software”) and any DACAST services purchased or otherwise made available from the DACAST Site (“DACAST Services” and “DACAST [Video Streaming Services](https://www.dacast.com/blog/choosing-a-live-video-streaming-solution-for-broadcasting-live-audio/ "Video Streaming Services")“) (collectively, the “DACAST Properties”). This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to all Users (“Users”) of the DACAST Properties.

#### 1\. WHAT INFORMATION DACAST COLLECTS FROM YOU

DACAST may collect two (2) types of information about you: Personal and Non-Personal.

##### 1.1 Personal Information

Personal Information refers to information that lets DACAST know the specifics of who you are and which may be used to identify, contact or locate you (e.g. name, mailing address, telephone number and e-mail address). DACAST may collect Personal Information when you use the DACAST Properties including, without limitation, setting up account information, filling out surveys, corresponding with DACAST, or otherwise volunteering information about yourself.

##### 1.2 Non-Personal Information

Non-Personal Information refers to information that, by itself, does not identify you as a specific individual (e.g. demographic information or website visitations). DACAST may collect Non-Personal Information through any of the methods discussed above as well as automatically through use of industry standard technologies described further below.

#### 2\. HOW DACAST COLLECTS YOUR INFORMATION

The Personal Information practices set forth apply to all DACAST’s customers worldwide.

##### 2.1. Registration

Prior to using one or more of the DACAST Properties, DACAST may require certain Personal Information and Non-Personal Information to create an individual account (“Account”) or to enable features or functionality of the DACAST Properties. Failure to provide all required information required by DACAST may prevent access to any or all DACAST Properties, and failure to maintain accurate information may result in suspension or termination of access to any or all DACAST Properties.

##### 2.2 Information Collected Through Technology

While you are able to visit the DACAST Site and remain anonymous, DACAST or its third party service providers may still collect Non-Personal Information about your use of the DACAST Properties (e.g. your Internet browser, operating system, IP address, connection speed, and the domain name of your Internet service provider). Such information may be gathered by the following methods:

(a) Cookies. Cookies, including local shared objects, are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive which work by assigning to your computer a unique number that has no meaning outside of the DACAST Site. Cookies do not generally contain any Personal Information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually configure your browser to prevent this. Not accepting cookies may make certain features of the DACAST Properties unavailable to you.

(b) IP Address. You may visit many areas of the DACAST Site anonymously without the need to become a registered User. Even in such cases, DACAST may collect IP addresses automatically. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you begin Services with an Internet services provider. Each time you access the DACAST Site and each time you request one of DACAST’s pages, the server logs your IP address.

(c) Web Beacons. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in web pages and e-mails. DACAST may use these technical methods in HTML e-mails that DACAST sends to Users to determine whether they have opened those e-mails and/or clicked on links in those e-mails. The information from use of these technical methods may be collected in a form that constitutes Personal Information.

(d) Tracking Content Usage. If you use the DACAST Services and you post audio visual materials including, without limitation, text, logos, artwork, graphics, pictures, advertisements, sound and other related intellectual property contained in such materials (collectively, “Content”) to your website or to a third party website, DACAST tracks and captures Non-Personal Information associated with User accounts and the use of Content.

#### 3\. HOW DACAST USES YOUR INFORMATION

##### 3.1 System Administration

DACAST may use Non-Personal Information for the purposes of system administration, assisting in diagnosing problems with DACAST servers, monitoring DACAST’s system performance and traffic on the DACAST Properties and to gather broad demographic information about DACAST customers.

##### 3.2 Personalization

DACAST uses Cookies and IP Addresses to track features such as delivering Content specific to your interests and informing you of new, relevant services or certain third party offerings.

##### 3.3 Notices to Registered Users

If you have registered for an Account, DACAST may use your Personal Information to send e-mails regarding your registration, including confirmation to verify the accuracy of any information you have provided, and instructions on how to post Content. DACAST may also send you e-mails to verify your identity or to notify you if DACAST believes your use of DACAST Properties violates any applicable agreement for the use of the DACAST Properties.

##### 3.4 Advertising

DACAST may use Non-Personal Information to assist in optimizing the delivery of advertisements to viewers of your Content.

##### 3.5 Promotional E-mails

DACAST may use your Personal Information to send you e-mails periodically listing promotions or events relating to the DACAST Properties or from DACAST’s marketing partners or sponsors. You have the choice to opt-out of receiving such promotional e-mails by sending an e-mail to [support@DACAST.com](mailto:support@dacast.com) and/or following the instructions in such correspondence. Once DACAST has processed your opt-out request, DACAST will not send you promotional e-mails unless you opt back in to receiving such communications.

##### 3.6 Contact Information

If you contact DACAST by telephone, e-mail or letter, DACAST may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence. If you report a problem with the DACAST Properties, DACAST may collect this information in a file specific to you. You may contact DACAST at [help@DACAST.com](mailto:help@dacast.com) to request the removal of this information from DACAST’s database.

#### 4\. HOW TO ACCESS AND CHANGE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Upon request, DACAST shall allow Users to update or correct Personal Information previously submitted, but only to the extent such activities will not compromise privacy or security interests. Additionally, upon request, DACAST shall delete Personal Information from the database where such information is stored; however, it may be impossible to entirely delete a User’s entry without some residual information being retained due to the manner in which data backups are maintained. Requests to delete Personal Information shall be submitted to [support@DACAST.com](mailto:support@dacast.com).

#### 5\. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES

DACAST does not sell, trade or rent Personal Information collected through the DACAST Properties to any third party. Notwithstanding the foregoing, DACAST shall: (1) fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies; and (2) may be required to disclose Personal Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation.

#### 6\. SAFEGUARDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

##### 6.1 Security Measures

DACAST takes appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of Personal Information. These include, but are not limited to, internal reviews of: (a) DACAST’s data collection; (b) storage and processing practices; (c) electronic security measures; and (d) physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where DACAST stores Personal Information. All DACAST employees, contractors and agents who access Personal Information are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution or unauthorized use or disclosure of Personal Information.

##### 6.2 Third-Party Links

The DACAST Properties may contain links to third parties who may collect Personal Information and Non-Personal Information directly from you. Additionally, DACAST may use third parties to provide components of the DACAST Properties. In either case, such third parties may have separate privacy policies and data collection practices, independent of DACAST. DACAST: (a) has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions; (b) is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites; and (c) does not make any warranties or representations about the contents, products or services offered on such websites or the security of any information you provide to them.

#### 7\. CHANGES TO DACAST’S PRIVACY POLICY

DACAST continually strives to implement new technologies and processes to better protect you, your privacy and your use of the DACAST Properties. As a result, changes to this Privacy Policy may be made by DACAST from time to time. In no event will these changes result in the degradation of any of the security measures designed to protect you from unauthorized disclosure, as such measures are described in this Privacy Policy.

#### 8\. SPECIAL NOTE REGARDING CHILDREN UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE

Use of the DACAST Properties is not intended for minors under the age of 18 (“Minors”). Minors are not authorized by DACAST to use the DACAST Properties, even if Minors set up an Account or accept the terms of any agreement for DACAST Properties. Parents or guardians may authorize Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 to use the DACAST Properties, provided they assume all responsibility and legal liability for the conduct of such Minor including, without limitation, monitoring the Minor’s access and use of the DACAST Properties. DACAST does not intentionally collect nor maintain any personally identifiable information from Minors. If you discover your Minor child has submitted his/her information to DACAST, you may request to have such information deleted from DACAST’s database by sending an e-mail request to [support@DACAST.com](mailto:support@dacast.com) together with the e-mail address that was submitted by the Minor. Upon receiving the request, DACAST shall delete such information within twenty (20) business days. If DACAST learns that a Minor is using the DACAST Properties, DACAST will require verified parental or guardian consent, in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”).

#### 9\. CONTACT DACAST

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy please contact DACAST by sending a letter or e-mail to: DACAST, LLC. Attn: Privacy 1175 Folsom street, San Francisco, CA 94103 [privacy@dacast.com](mailto:privacy@dacast.com)
